http://www.jaanj.com/about/privacy/

FREE GIFT with orders over $200 subtotal
FREE SHIPPING for all USA orders over $75. NO SALES TAX
FREE SHIPPING  worldwide for all international orders over $100. NO SALES TAX
CART (0) - $0.00
FREE GIFT with orders over $200 subtotal
FREE SHIPPING for all USA orders over $75. NO SALES TAX
FREE SHIPPING  worldwide for all international orders over $100. NO SALES TAX
SALE
Slim - 3"
PETA
Traditional - 3 ¾"
Classic
Signature
Skinny - 2 ¼"
Our Commitment to Privacy
jaanj.com respects the privacy of our customers. Jaan J. collects customers' information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products and services. Jaan J. does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.
This policy describes the personal information Jaan J. collects about you, why Jaan J. collects it and. uses it.
Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how Jaan J. collects and uses your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always write to jaanj.com's customer service in any of two ways:
Via Email
Fill out our Contact Us page.
Jaan. J.
750 3rd Avenue 120532
Chula Vista, CA 91912
If our information practices change in the future, Jaan J. will post an updated policy on our jaanj.com website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the end of this policy. You may implement your choices about how Jaan J. gathers and uses your information at any time.
What kind of information does jaanj.com collect?
Jaan J. gathers information, such as your name, e-mail, postal addresses, and phone numbers from you when you visit jaanj.com.
Jaan J. upholds a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online.
How does jaanj.com use my information?
When you place an order or make a purchase from jaanj.com, Jaan J. uses your personal information to process your order, send you e-mails to confirm your order or contacts you via phone, postal mail or e-mail regarding your order or other questions Jaan J. may have.
When you place an order, make a purchase or save your information online, Jaan J. may use your e-mail, postal address and personal information to send you information about our products and services.
Jaan J. may use this information to contact you via e-mail, postal mail, or telephone to learn more about your shopping preferences. You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls.
Does jaanj.com share my information with third parties?
Jaan J. reserves the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of Jaan J.
How do I access my information? How do I change or delete my information?
You can update or delete certain personal information related to your use of our online site (e.g., name and contact information). Simply access your account information and edit your personal information. You can ask us to update or delete your personal information by writing us at:
Via Email
Fill out our Contact Us page.
Jaan. J.
750 3rd Avenue 120532
Chula Vista, CA 91912
Please be sure to include your full name and the e-mail address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from us. Please be advised that all requests to update your personal information may take up to ten days for your e-mail request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.
How do I exercise my choices about receiving promotional communications?
Jaan J. wants to communicate with you. If you prefer not to receive promotional information from us, or if you do not want us to use your information to enhance your shopping experience, please let us know by writing us at:
Via Email
Fill out our Contact Us page.
Jaan. J.
750 3rd Avenue 120532
Chula Vista, CA 91912
Please be advised to include your full name and the e-mail address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from us. If you ask us to remove your name and address from our lists, Jaan J. will maintain your name in a "Do Not Contact" file to ensure that Jaan J. can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your e-mail request, and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Jaan J.
Please note that when you purchase from us, Jaan J. will continue to confirm your order by e-mail.
Jaan J. may also need to contact you via phone, e-mail or postal mail with other questions regarding your order.
How does jaanj.com protect kids' privacy?
Jaan J. is concerned about the protection of children when they use the Internet.
Jaan J. will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.
What are cookies? How does jaanj.com use cookies on its site?
A cookie is a small data file that websites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information, such as a unique user ID that websites use to track the pages of the sites you've visited. Jaan J. uses cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.
Jaan J. uses cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. Cookies allow us to keep track of your order as you shop on our site. Through our use of cookies, Jaan J. also tracks and preserves the identity of the website you visited immediately before visiting jaanj.com.
Jaan J. does not track any information about your use of other websites.
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, Jaan J. will not be able to track your order to enable you to purchase from our site. Jaan J. will not be able to recognize you as a registered user, which allows you to access your account information.
Credit Card Safety?
Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank or credit card company cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of unauthorized or fraudulent charges on a credit card.
Protecting your order information is important to us. Jaan J. uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your online order information as it is transmitted over the Internet.
Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers like the ones Jaan J. uses to process orders at jaanj.com. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower portion of your browser window after accessing the server.
If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then the SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https."
If your browser or firewall doesn't support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server, which means you won't be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please order by emailing us at cs@jaanj.com.
State the item(s) you would like to purchase and a representative will contact you within 24 business hours to process your purchase.
If someone steals your credit card information or uses your credit card in an unauthorized manner on our site (as determined by your credit card company) - through no fault of your own - Jaan J. will NOT cover any charges your credit card company doesn't.
If you're not quite comfortable shopping online, or would prefer to make your purchase via other means, just e-mail us at cs@jaanj.com and a representative will call you within 24 business hours to take your order. Please be sure to have your information on hand in order to expedite your purchase(s).
What about links to other websites and services?
jaanj.com may contain links to other sites. Jaan J. does not control the privacy policies or practices of these websites. You should review those policies before providing any personal information. Jaan J. is not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites and Jaan J. provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
English
Français
Deutsch
Ties
Accessories
PETA
Sale
About
Return to Jaan J.
BACK
Slim - 3"
Traditional - 3 ¾"
Classic
Signature
Skinny - 2 ¼"
About Jaan J.
